This is my renal lodge, I place it above my renal lodge.
ここは私の腎臓のロッジです。腎臓のロッジの上に置きます。
I am in the axis behind here of the omental bursa and all this relationship of
私は、ここにある後腹膜腔の後ろの軸の中にいます。そして、この胃との関係全体は、
the stomach,
胃の、
but in its posterior part.
しかし、その後部においてです。
This growth movement of my liver will perform all this movement
私の肝臓のこの成長の動きは、このすべての動きを引き起こします。
of sub-diaphragmatic tilting
横隔膜下の傾斜の、
and gastric placement, but also, we
そして胃の配置の、しかしさらに、私たちは、
go further, what is called,
さらに進んで、私たちが呼ぶところの、
the retro-gastric pouch, the placement of the devil.
つまり、後胃嚢、悪魔の配置です。
of the omentum, of the spleen, etc., will depend on this enormous growth of my liver.
脾臓などの配置は、私の肝臓のこの巨大な成長に依存します。
All this system, on a fascial level, and this is a reference axis that we must have,
このシステム全体は、顔面平面上では、そしてこれは私たちが持つべき参照軸ですが、
is suspended from my aorta.
私の大動脈に吊り下げられています。
This is where all the trophic gateway passes.
そこがすべての栄養供給の門が通るところです。
It's as if it also revolves around the aortic system, you see?
まるで大動脈系を中心に回っているかのようでしょう？
As if there was an aortic axis here, and the balance point will be made around here.
ここに大動脈の軸があり、バランスのポイントがその周りで起こるかのようです。
And you see how the stomach, finally, will, with this movement, follow
そして、胃が、最終的に、この動きにどのように追従するかがわかるでしょう。
this process.
このプロセスに。
I brace myself like this, then I come slightly above
私はこのように落ち着き、そして少し上に移動します。
the rib cage here, and there, I have, in fact...
ここのグリルに、そしてそこには、実際には...
Thank you.
ありがとうございます。
I'm exaggerating the movement for you.
皆さんのために動きを誇張しています。
This is its pure developmental movement.
これは、その純粋な発生的な動きです。
I'm going to listen embryonically.
私はむしろ胚的な聴診に集中します。
First thing, my neutral.
まず、私のニュートラル。
My hands are placed and encompass well, lightly.
私の手は置かれ、軽く、しっかりと包み込んでいます。
The image is ants.
イメージはアリです。
You shouldn't kill them, but they shouldn't leave.
殺してはいけませんが、逃がしてもいけません。
In my head, I have the vascular axis.
私の頭の中には、血管軸があります。
aortic behind. I have the end of the exhalation, I enter and I
後ろの大動脈。呼気の終わりがあり、私は入り込み、そして、
wait. I put myself in this
待ちます。私はこの、
quality. The liver here, it's that it comes to seek something at its source. It
その質の中に身を置きます。ここにある肝臓は、その源から何かを探し求めているのです。それは、
needs to go back a little. I let it. First feeling, instead of
少し後ろに戻る必要があります。私はそれを任せます。最初の感覚は、
having
持つ代わりに、
this imprint that makes this movement well, it's not entirely free. So it
この動きをうまく行うこの痕跡は、完全に自由ではありません。だから、それは、
seeks to regenerate something. Point of support here, with my elbow, but not too
何かを再生しようとしています。ここでの支点は、私の肘を使いますが、あまり強くありません。
strong. I give the point of support with my breathing.
強く。私は呼吸で支点を与えます。
primary I let the neutral settle and I let the system come we will
一次呼吸で、私はノートが落ち着くのを許し、システムが来るのを許します。私たちは、
take the axis of the caval heart in fact it's a little more like this if I
心臓の軸を取ります。実際、それはもう少しこのように、もし私が、
have to put myself in the movement of consciousness
意識の動きに身を置くなら、
of space the opening of
空間の、開口部の。
space the
空間
perception of this space secondly
この空間の知覚、第二に
the notion of the neutral
中立の概念
of the patient
患者の
when this neutral
この中立が
begins to mature
成熟し始めるとき
little by little
少しずつ
then the two neutrals
すると二つの中立が
meet
出会う
and this process
そしてこのプロセスが
becomes the therapeutic process
治療プロセスとなる
we are a patient
私たちは患者であり
and as we create
そして私たちが創造するように
a space
空間を
of impatience, there is no such encounter here, there is just this happening.
焦りの、ここにはこの出会いはなく、ただそれが起こるだけです。
The process is there, now I can work.
プロセスはそこにある、そこで私は働くことができる。
It's about, at a given moment, daring to let the primary respiration work.
それはある時点で、一次呼吸に働くことを許すことです。
And there, I know we want to, but we can also do this practice.
そして、私たちはそうしたいと知っていますが、この練習も非常によくできます。
I sometimes teach, here I'm teaching you a bit
私は時々教えていますが、ここでは少し教えています
this energetic, embryonic level
このエネルギーレベル、胚性レベル
but we can very well do it
しかし、私たちは非常によくそれを行うことができます
through fascial planes
筋膜の平面によって
etcetera too, no problem
などでも問題ありません
my observation
私の観察では
is that it doesn't hold well
それはうまくいかない